Register of the Gerald Lee Warren papers, 1956-1994
Hoover Institution Archives
- White House Subject File, 1969-1977 (Boxes 90-217)
  - Watergate
    - 1969-1973 June
      - Press conferences
        - 1972
          - October (Box-folder 195: 52)
        - 1973 February-June (Box-folder 196: 1-5)
      - Press releases
        - General (Box-folder 196: 6)
        - 1973
          - January (Box-folder 196: 7)
          - March (Box-folder 196: 8)
          - May (Box-folder 196: 9)
      - Printed matter, 1973 May (Box-folder 196: 10)
      - Remarks
        - Undated (Box-folder 196: 11)
        - 1973 April (Box-folder 196: 12)
      - Schedules, 1972 June (Box-folder 196: 13)
      - Special prosecutor, 1973 May (Box-folder 196: 14)
      - Statements
        - Undated (Box-folder 196: 15)
        - 1972 January (Box-folder 196: 16)
        - 1973 February-May (Box-folder 196: 17-20)
      - Tape chronology (Box-folder 196: 21)
      - Telegrams
        - 1972 January (Box-folder 196: 22)
        - 1973 May (Box-folder 196: 23)
      - Television news reports
        - Undated (Box-folder 196: 24)
        - 1972
          - August (Box-folder 196: 25)
          - October (Box-folder 196: 26)
        - 1973
          - January (Box-folder 196: 27)
          - March-May (Box-folder 196: 28-30)
      - Testimonies, 1973 May-June (Box-folder 196: 31-32)
    - 1973 July-December
      - Affidavits (Box-folder 197: 1)
      - Correspondence
        - Undated (Box-folder 197: 2)
        - 1973 July-December (Box-folder 197: 3-8)
      - Court proceedings, 1973 July-December (Box-folder 197: 9-14)
      - General (Box-folder 197: 15)
      - Interviews, 1973
        - July-August (Box-folder 197: 16-17)
        - October-December (Box-folder 197: 18-20)
      - Meetings
        - Undated (Box-folder 197: 21)
        - 1973 November (Box-folder 197: 22)
      - Memoranda, 1973
        - July-August (Box-folder 197: 23-24)
        - October-December (Box-folder 197: 25-27)
      - News summaries
        - Undated (Box-folder 198: 1)
        - 1973 August-December (Box-folder 198: 2-6)
      - Press briefings, 1973 October-November (Box-folder 198: 7-8)
      - Press conferences
        - Undated (Box-folder 198: 9)
        - 1973 July-August (Box-folder 198: 10-11)
        - 1973 October-December (Box-folder 198: 12-14)
      - Press releases
        - Undated (Box-folder 198: 15)
        - 1973 October-December (Box-folder 198: 16-18)
      - Printed matter, 1973 July (Box-folder 198: 19)
      - Remarks, 1973
        - July-August (Box-folder 198: 20-21)
        - October-December (Box-folder 198: 22-24)
      - Statements
        - Undated (Box-folder 198: 25)
        - 1973 July-August (Box-folder 198: 26-27)
        - 1973 October-December (Box-folder 198: 28-30)
      - Telegrams, undated (Box-folder 198: 31)
      - Television news reports
        - Undated (Box-folder 198: 32)
        - 1973 August (Box-folder 198: 33)
        - 1973 October-December (Box-folder 198: 34-36)
    - 1974 January-December
      - Correspondence, 1974
        - January-February (Box-folder 198: 37-38)
        - April-July (Box-folder 198: 39-42)
        - September (Box-folder 198: 43)
      - Court proceedings, 1974 February-August (Box-folder 199: 1-7)
      - Fact sheets
        - Undated (Box-folder 199: 8)
        - 1974 January-February (Box-folder 199: 9-10)
        - 1974 April-May (Box-folder 199: 11-12)
        - 1974 July (Box-folder 199: 13)
      - Correspondence, 1974 May-June (Box-folder 199: 14-15)
      - House Judiciary Committee
        - Fact sheets
          - 1974 April (Box-folder 199: 16)
          - 1974 May-July (Box-folder 200: 1-4)
          - 1974 September (Box-folder 200: 5)
            Printed copies.
        - General (Box-folder 200: 6)
        - Impeachment
          - General (Box-folder 200: 7)
          - I, A-F (Box-folder 200: 8)
          - I, G-Appendix A (Box-folder 200: 9)
          - II-IV (Box-folder 200: 10-11)
      - Interviews
        - Undated (Box-folder 200: 12)
        - 1974 January-April (Box-folder 200: 13-16)
        - 1974 May (Box-folder 201: 1)
        - 1974 July (Box-folder 201: 2)
        - 1974 October (Box-folder 201: 3)
      - Meetings
        - Undated (Box-folder 201: 4)
        - 1974 June (Box-folder 201: 5)
      - Memoranda
        - Undated (Box-folder 201: 6)
        - 1974 January-July (Box-folder 201: 7-13)
          Includes printed materials.
        - 1974 September (Box-folder 201: 14)
      - News summaries
        - Undated (Box-folder 201: 15)
        - 1974 January-February (Box-folder 201: 16-17)
        - 1974 April-June (Box-folder 201: 18-20)
        - 1974 September-October (Box-folder 201: 21-22)
      - Pool reports
        - 1974 April (Box-folder 201: 23)
        - 1974 July (Box-folder 201: 24)
      - Press briefings
        - Undated (Box-folder 201: 25)
        - 1974 February-March (Box-folder 201: 26-27)
        - 1974 May-July (Box-folder 201: 28-30)
      - Press conferences
        - Undated (Box-folder 202: 1)
        - 1974 January-September (Box-folder 202: 2-10)
      - Press releases
        - Undated (Box-folder 202: 11)
        - 1974 January (Box-folder 202: 12)
        - 1974 March (Box-folder 202: 13)
        - 1974 May-July (Box-folder 202: 14-16)
      - Printed matter
        - Undated (Box-folder 202: 17)
        - 1974 October (Box-folder 202: 18)
      - Proclamations, 1974 September (Box-folder 202: 19)
      - Remarks
        - Undated (Box-folder 202: 20)
        - 1974 February (Box-folder 202: 21)
        - 1974 April (Box-folder 202: 22)
        - 1974 June-July (Box-folder 202: 23-24)
          Includes telephone conversation.
        - 1974 September (Box-folder 202: 25)
      - Reports
        - 1974 January-February (Box-folder 202: 26-27)
        - 1974 May (Box-folder 202: 28)
      - Schedules, 1974 April (Box-folder 203: 1)
      - Senate Select Committee proceedings, 1974 January-March (Box-folder 203: 2-4)
      - Statements
        - Undated (Box-folder 203: 5)
        - 1974 January-March (Box-folder 203: 6-8)
        - 1974 May-November (Box-folder 203: 9-15)
      - Supreme Court proceedings
        - Briefs (printed copies)
          - Undated (Box-folder 203: 16)
          - 1974 July (Box-folder 203: 17)
        - Fact sheets, 1974 June-July (Box-folder 203: 18-19)
        - Press briefings, 1974 June (Box-folder 203: 20)
        - Wire releases, 1974 July (Box-folder 203: 21)
      - Telegrams
        - 1974 March-April (Box-folder 203: 22-23)
        - 1974 June-July (Box-folder 203: 24-25)
      - Television news reports
        - Undated (Box-folder 203: 26)
        - 1974 January-March (Box-folder 203: 27-29)
        - 1974 April-August (Box-folder 204: 1-5)
      - Testimonies, 1974 October (Box-folder 204: 6)
    - News summaries, 1975 May (Box-folder 204: 7)
  - White House staff and presidential appointees
    - Correspondence
      - 1970
        - Undated (Box-folder 204: 8)
        - May-August (Box-folder 204: 9-12)
        - December (Box-folder 204: 13)
      - 1971
        - January-February (Box-folder 204: 14-15)
        - July (Box-folder 204: 16)
        - October-December (Box-folder 204: 17-19)
      - 1972
        - January-April (Box-folder 204: 20-23)
        - June (Box-folder 204: 24)
        - November (Box-folder 204: 25)
      - 1973
        - January-February (Box-folder 204: 26-27)
        - April-August (Box-folder 204: 28-32)
        - October (Box-folder 204: 33)
      - 1974
        - February (Box-folder 204: 34)
        - June-July (Box-folder 204: 35-36)
        - October-November (Box-folder 204: 37-38)
      - 1975
        - March (Box-folder 204: 39)
        - June-July (Box-folder 204: 40-41)
    - Court proceedings, 1973 June (Box-folder 204: 42)
    - Curriculum vitae
      - Undated (Box-folder 204: 43)
      - 1969 February (Box-folder 204: 44)
      - 1970-1975 (Box-folder 204: 45-50)
    - Executive orders
      - 1970
        - April (Box-folder 205: 1)
        - July (Box-folder 205: 2)
        - October (Box-folder 205: 3)
      - 1971 December (Box-folder 205: 4)
      - 1972 December (Box-folder 205: 5)
      - 1973 April-May (Box-folder 205: 6-7)
      - 1974
        - February-April (Box-folder 205: 8-10)
        - June (Box-folder 205: 11)
      - 1975 May-June (Box-folder 205: 12-13)
    - Fact sheets
      - Undated (Box-folder 205: 14)
      - 1969 September (Box-folder 205: 15)
      - 1970
        - February (Box-folder 205: 16)
        - April (Box-folder 205: 17)
        - December (Box-folder 205: 18)
      - 1971
        - April (Box-folder 205: 19)
        - June (Box-folder 205: 20)
        - September (Box-folder 205: 21)
      - 1972 November (Box-folder 205: 22)
      - 1973
        - February (Box-folder 205: 23)
        - May (Box-folder 205: 24)
      - 1974 December (Box-folder 205: 25)
    - Handbook, 1975 (Box-folder 205: 26)
    - Kissinger, Henry
      - Clippings, 1975 May (Box-folder 205: 27)
      - Correspondence
        - Undated (Box-folder 205: 28)
        - 1971 January (Box-folder 205: 29)
        - 1972 August (Box-folder 205: 30)
        - 1973 November (Box-folder 205: 31)
        - 1974
          - June (Box-folder 205: 32)
          - August (Box-folder 205: 33)
      - Fact sheets
        - 1972 September (Box-folder 205: 34)
        - 1973 September-October (Box-folder 205: 35-36)
        - 1974
          - May (Box-folder 205: 37)
          - December (Box-folder 205: 38)
      - General (Box-folder 205: 39)
      - Interviews
        - Undated (Box-folder 205: 40)
        - 1972 December (Box-folder 205: 41)
        - 1973
          - February (Box-folder 205: 42)
          - November (Box-folder 205: 43)
        - 1974 December (Box-folder 205: 44)
        - 1975
          - January (Box-folder 205: 45)
          - April-July (Box-folder 205: 46-49)
      - Meetings
        - Undated (Box-folder 205: 50)
        - 1970 January (Box-folder 205: 51)
        - 1972
          - May (Box-folder 205: 52)
          - July (Box-folder 205: 53)
          - March (Box-folder 206: 1)
          - September-October (Box-folder 206: 2-3)
        - 1974 May-September (Box-folder 206: 4-8)
        - 1975 June (Box-folder 206: 9)
      - Memoranda
        - Undated (Box-folder 206: 10)
        - 1969
          - February (Box-folder 206: 11)
          - July-August (Box-folder 206: 12-13)
          - November-December (Box-folder 206: 14-15)
        - 1970
          - January-March (Box-folder 206: 16-18)
          - May (Box-folder 206: 19)
          - July (Box-folder 206: 20)
          - November (Box-folder 206: 21)
        - 1971
          - January-April (Box-folder 206: 22-25)
          - June (Box-folder 206: 26)
          - September (Box-folder 206: 27)
          - November (Box-folder 206: 28)
        - 1972
          - January-March (Box-folder 206: 29-31)
          - June-July (Box-folder 206: 32-33)
          - October (Box-folder 206: 34)
        - 1973
          - January-February (Box-folder 206: 35-36)
          - May (Box-folder 206: 37)
        - 1974
          - February (Box-folder 206: 38)
          - June (Box-folder 206: 39)
        - 1975
          - April (Box-folder 206: 40)
          - June (Box-folder 206: 41)
      - Miscellaneous (Box-folder 206: 42)
        Includes poster and holograph note.
      - Newsletters, 1975 July (Box-folder 206: 43)
      - News summaries
        - Undated (Box-folder 206: 44)
        - 1972 October (Box-folder 206: 45)
        - 1974
          - June (Box-folder 206: 46)
          - September (Box-folder 206: 47)
        - 1975 April-May (Box-folder 206: 48-49)
      - Pool reports
        - Undated (Box-folder 206: 50)
        - 1972 July (Box-folder 206: 51)
        - 1973 September (Box-folder 206: 52)
        - 1974 March (Box-folder 206: 53)
      - Press briefings
        - Undated (Box-folder 206: 54)
        - 1969
          - May (Box-folder 206: 55)
          - November-December (Box-folder 206: 56-57)
        - 1970
          - February (Box-folder 206: 58)
          - April-June (Box-folder 206: 59-61)
          - August-December (Box-folder 207: 1-5)
        - 1971
          - February (Box-folder 207: 6)
          - April-May (Box-folder 207: 7-8)
          - July (Box-folder 207: 9)
          - October-December (Box-folder 207: 10-12)
        - 1972
          - January (Box-folder 207: 13)
          - April-June (Box-folder 207: 14-16)
        - 1973
          - January (Box-folder 207: 17)
          - April (Box-folder 207: 18)
        - 1974
          - February-March (Box-folder 207: 19-20)
          - May-July (Box-folder 207: 21-23)
        - 1975
          - February (Box-folder 207: 24)
          - April (Box-folder 207: 25)
      - Press conferences
        - Undated (Box-folder 207: 26)
        - 1971
          - February-March (Box-folder 207: 27-28)
          - October-November (Box-folder 207: 29-30)
        - 1972
          - January-February (Box-folder 207: 31-32)
          - April-May (Box-folder 207: 33-34)
          - June (Box-folder 208: 1)
          - September-October (Box-folder 208: 2-3)
          - December (Box-folder 208: 4)
        - 1973
          - January-February (Box-folder 208: 5-6)
          - May-June (Box-folder 208: 7-8)
          - August-October (Box-folder 208: 9-11)
          - December (Box-folder 208: 12)
        - 1974
          - January-April (Box-folder 208: 13-16)
          - June-July (Box-folder 208: 17-18)
          - October-December (Box-folder 208: 19-21)
        - 1975
          - January-July (Box-folder 209: 1-7)
          - December (Box-folder 209: 8)
      - Press releases
        - Undated (Box-folder 209: 9)
        - 1971 August (Box-folder 209: 10)
        - 1973
          - February (Box-folder 209: 11)
          - September-October (Box-folder 209: 12-13)
        - 1974
          - February (Box-folder 209: 14)
          - May-June (Box-folder 209: 15-16)
      - Printed matter
        - 1970 January (Box-folder 209: 17)
        - 1973 October (Box-folder 209: 18)
        - 1974
          - June (Box-folder 209: 19)
          - September (Box-folder 209: 20)
        - 1975 April-June (Box-folder 209: 21-23)
      - Remarks
        - Undated (Box-folder 209: 24)
        - 1968 December (Box-folder 209: 25)
        - 1971 October (Box-folder 209: 26)
        - 1972 January (Box-folder 209: 27)
        - 1973
          - April (Box-folder 209: 28)
          - July-October (Box-folder 209: 29-32)
          - December (Box-folder 209: 33)
        - 1974
          - February (Box-folder 209: 34)
          - April (Box-folder 209: 35)
          - July-November (Box-folder 209: 36-40)
            Includes a printed copy.
        - 1975
          - February-March (Box-folder 209: 41-42)
          - May-July (Box-folder 209: 43-45)
      - Schedules
        - Undated (Box-folder 209: 46)
        - 1973
          - February (Box-folder 209: 47)
          - September (Box-folder 209: 48)
      - Statements
        - Undated (Box-folder 210: 1)
        - 1972 June (Box-folder 210: 2)
        - 1973 September-December (Box-folder 210: 3-6)
        - 1974
          - January-February (Box-folder 210: 7-8)
          - April-May (Box-folder 210: 9-10)
          - August-September (Box-folder 210: 11-12)
        - 1975
          - May (Box-folder 210: 13)
          - November (Box-folder 210: 14)
      - Telegrams, 1974
        - May-June (Box-folder 210: 15-16)
        - November (Box-folder 210: 17)
      - Television news reports
        - 1971 March (Box-folder 210: 18)
        - 1972
          - June (Box-folder 210: 19)
          - October (Box-folder 210: 20)
        - 1973 July-December (Box-folder 210: 21-26)
        - 1974
          - January (Box-folder 210: 27)
          - April-August (Box-folder 210: 28-32)
          - November (Box-folder 210: 33)
      - Testimonies, 1973 September (Box-folder 210: 34)
      - Wire releases, 1972 December (Box-folder 210: 35)
      - Writings by, undated (Box-folder 210: 36)
    - Interviews
      - Undated (Box-folder 210: 37)
      - 1970
        - July (Box-folder 210: 38)
        - December (Box-folder 210: 39)
      - 1974 January (Box-folder 210: 40)
      - 1975 February (Box-folder 210: 41)
    - Meetings
      - 1970
        - January (Box-folder 210: 42)
        - August (Box-folder 210: 43)
        - November-December (Box-folder 210: 44-45)
      - 1971
        - January-February (Box-folder 210: 46-47)
        - April (Box-folder 210: 48)
        - June-December (Box-folder 210: 49-55)
      - 1972
        - May-June (Box-folder 210: 56-57)
        - August (Box-folder 210: 58)
      - 1974 September (Box-folder 210: 59)
      - 1975 June (Box-folder 210: 60)
    - Memoranda
      - Undated (Box-folder 211: 1)
      - 1968 August (Box-folder 211: 2)
      - 1969
        - February (Box-folder 211: 3)
        - May (Box-folder 211: 4)
        - August (Box-folder 211: 5)
        - October (Box-folder 211: 6)
        - December (Box-folder 211: 7)
      - 1970
        - March-May (Box-folder 211: 8-10)
        - July-September (Box-folder 211: 11-13)
        - December (Box-folder 211: 14)
      - 1971
        - January-March (Box-folder 211: 15-17)
        - June-July (Box-folder 211: 18-19)
        - September (Box-folder 211: 20)
        - December (Box-folder 211: 21)
      - 1972
        - January-February (Box-folder 211: 22-23)
        - April (Box-folder 211: 24)
        - June-July (Box-folder 211: 25-26)
        - November-December (Box-folder 211: 27-28)
      - 1973
        - January (Box-folder 211: 29)
        - May-August (Box-folder 211: 30-33)
        - November (Box-folder 211: 34)
      - 1974
        - February (Box-folder 211: 35)
        - June-October (Box-folder 211: 36-40)
        - December (Box-folder 211: 41)
      - 1975
        - January (Box-folder 211: 42)
        - May-July (Box-folder 211: 43-45)
    - Messages (printed copy), 1970 June (Box-folder 211: 46)
    - Newsletters
      - 1970 May (Box-folder 211: 47)
      - 1973 May (Box-folder 211: 48)
      - 1975 July (Box-folder 211: 49)
    - News summaries
      - Undated (Box-folder 211: 50)
      - 1970
        - May (Box-folder 211: 51)
        - September (Box-folder 211: 52)
        - December (Box-folder 211: 53)
      - 1971
        - March-April (Box-folder 211: 54-55)
        - June (Box-folder 211: 56)
      - 1972 July-August (Box-folder 211: 57-58)
    - Pool reports, 1973 April (Box-folder 211: 59)
    - Press briefings
      - Undated (Box-folder 211: 60)
      - 1970 May (Box-folder 211: 61)
      - 1971
        - February (Box-folder 211: 62)
        - April (Box-folder 211: 63)
        - August (Box-folder 211: 64)
      - 1973
        - March (Box-folder 211: 65)
        - August (Box-folder 211: 66)
      - 1974 September-October (Box-folder 211: 67-68)
      - 1975 April (Box-folder 211: 69)
    - Press conferences
      - Undated (Box-folder 211: 70)
      - 1968 December (Box-folder 211: 71)
      - 1969 January (Box-folder 211: 72)
      - 1970 May (Box-folder 211: 73)
      - 1972
        - February (Box-folder 211: 74)
        - November (Box-folder 211: 75)
      - 1973
        - January (Box-folder 211: 76)
        - February (Box-folder 212: 1)
      - 1974 May (Box-folder 212: 2)
    - Press releases
      - Undated (Box-folder 212: 3)
      - 1969
        - February (Box-folder 212: 4)
        - August-September (Box-folder 212: 5-6)
        - November-December (Box-folder 212: 7-8)
      - 1970 February-December (Box-folder 212: 9-19)
      - 1971 (Box-folder 212: 20-31)
      - 1972 (Box-folder 213: 1-12)
      - 1973 (Box-folder 213: 13-24)
      - 1974
        - January-May (Box-folder 213: 25-29)
        - June-December (Box-folder 214: 1-7)
      - 1975 January-July (Box-folder 214: 8-14)
    - Printed matter
      - 1969 November (Box-folder 214: 15)
      - 1971 June (Box-folder 214: 16)
      - 1975 March (Box-folder 214: 17)
    - Remarks
      - Undated (Box-folder 214: 18)
      - 1968 December (Box-folder 214: 19)
      - 1970
        - May-June (Box-folder 214: 20-21)
        - September (Box-folder 214: 22)
        - December (Box-folder 214: 23)
      - 1971
        - February (Box-folder 214: 24)
        - December (Box-folder 214: 25)
      - 1972 June (Box-folder 214: 26)
      - 1973
        - February-March (Box-folder 214: 27-28)
        - November (Box-folder 214: 29)
      - 1974
        - March (Box-folder 214: 30)
        - May-June (Box-folder 214: 31-32)
      - 1975 March-June (Box-folder 214: 33-36)
    - Reports, 1972 June (Box-folder 214: 37)
    - Schedules
      - 1970
        - February (Box-folder 214: 38)
        - September (Box-folder 214: 39)
      - 1971
        - January-February (Box-folder 214: 40-41)
        - April (Box-folder 214: 42)
        - June (Box-folder 214: 43)
      - 1972 December (Box-folder 214: 44)
    - Secret service
      - General (Box-folder 214: 45)
      - Memoranda, 1968 November (Box-folder 214: 46)
      - Press releases, 1973 May (Box-folder 214: 47)
      - Television news reports, 1973 February (Box-folder 214: 48)
    - Standards of conduct (Box-folder 214: 49)
    - Statements
      - Undated (Box-folder 214: 50)
      - 1970
        - June-July (Box-folder 214: 51-52)
        - October (Box-folder 214: 53)
        - December (Box-folder 214: 54)
      - 1971 September (Box-folder 214: 55)
      - 1972
        - January (Box-folder 214: 56)
        - March (Box-folder 214: 57)
        - July (Box-folder 214: 58)
        - November-December (Box-folder 214: 59-60)
      - 1973 April-May (Box-folder 214: 61-62)
      - 1974
        - January (Box-folder 215: 1)
        - September (Box-folder 215: 2)
    - Telegrams
      - 1970 June (Box-folder 215: 3)
      - 1973 October (Box-folder 215: 4)
    - Telephone directory (includes booklet) (Box-folder 215: 5)
    - Television news reports
      - 1970 June (Box-folder 215: 6)
      - 1972 November (Box-folder 215: 7)
      - 1973
        - June (Box-folder 215: 8)
        - September-October (Box-folder 215: 9-10)
      - 1974 August (Box-folder 215: 11)
    - Testimonies (printed copy), 1975 November (Box-folder 215: 12)
    - Vice presidents
      - Correspondence
        - 1969 February (Box-folder 215: 13)
        - 1973
          - July-September (Box-folder 215: 14-16)
          - November (Box-folder 215: 17)
        - 1974 January (Box-folder 215: 18)
      - Court proceedings, 1973 October (Box-folder 215: 19)
      - Curriculum vitae (printed copy) (Box-folder 215: 20)
      - Fact sheets
        - Undated (Box-folder 215: 21)
        - 1970
          - August (Box-folder 215: 22)
          - November (Box-folder 215: 23)
        - 1974 January (Box-folder 215: 24)
      - Interviews
        - Undated (Box-folder 215: 25)
        - 1970
          - February (Box-folder 215: 26)
          - September (Box-folder 215: 27)
        - 1972 February (Box-folder 215: 28)
          Transcript.
        - 1973 December (Box-folder 215: 29)
        - 1974 January-February (Box-folder 215: 30-31)
        - 1975 May (Box-folder 215: 32)
      - Meetings
        - 1970 September (Box-folder 215: 33)
        - 1971 September (Box-folder 215: 34)
        - 1973 October (Box-folder 215: 35)
      - Memoranda
        - Undated (Box-folder 215: 36)
        - 1970 September (Box-folder 215: 37)
        - 1973 October (Box-folder 215: 38)
        - 1974
          - January (Box-folder 215: 39)
          - August (Box-folder 215: 40)
      - Newsletters, 1973 November (Box-folder 215: 41)
      - News summaries
        - 1970
          - September (Box-folder 215: 42)
          - December (Box-folder 215: 43)
        - 1971 July (Box-folder 215: 44)
        - 1973
          - October (Box-folder 215: 45)